Boggle is a word game that is played on a 4x4 board with 16 letter tiles. 
The goal is to find as many words as possible given a time constraint.  
For this exercise, we are making one modification.  Now it is possible for one or more of the letter tiles to be blank (denoted by *).  
When a tile is blank, it can be treated as any other letter.  Note that in one game it does not have to be the same character for each word.  
For example, if the tiles C, T, and * are adjacent.  The words cot, cat, and cut can all be used. 
You will be given a text file containing all valid English words (a dictionary).
You will also be given an initial board configuration as a text file with commas separating the letters. Use this as a guide for how 
To set up the board

For example a file may contain:

A, C, E, D, L, U, G, *, E, *, H, T, G, A, F, K

This is equivalent to the board:

A C E D
L U G *
E * H T
G A F K

Some sample words from this board are ace, dug, eight, hole, huge, hug, tide.  

Design and Implement an API in a language of your choice that lets a user play a game of Boggle. At the very least, a user should be able to query the current board as well as check if a word is on the board. Be as creative as you’d like. Include a short README explaining your chosen design.

You can do this on your own time. Send us your solution whenever you’re done. Your solution should include an actual implementation hosted somewhere for us to play with. 